I propose an A for my course grade. I believe my code was comparable to the posted solutions, all of my submitted assignments were functionally working and included comments and the why behind the written code. I did not miss more than five meetings and was always present in the class lectures (especially dynamic programming). I spent time outside class attempting to improve my understanding of certain topics, such as the min flow max cut, dynamic programming, and the Neural Networks lecture. I did not fully grasp these concepts from just the notebook and lectures so I was led to the O'Reilly collection and other online sources for explanation. Even though I did not ask/answer many questions throughout the class lecture I was always engaged and in attendance, showing a level of overall engagement. 
